the psychological pressure of hearing that
maybe you're an idiot, you have to do
something different and we'll have it too
.  The four of us co-founders have a very
tight control over the
majority, so we
listen to investors' input with humility, but
there's no one who can force us.
This is often detrimental because if you
have teams of executive managers who
are effectively hired, if they don't deliver
good results in the quarter, the
board of directors might fire them
and therefore they feel a lot of pressure even
if they think that that action isn't
the best one for the next three years and to
show something good in the short term.
This does not apply to us for better or for
worse, we have the ability to
control the fate, let's say, of the
management of the company and therefore we are
somewhat shielded.